Great, I'll do that when I wanna
be the first guy in space to get a wedgie.
(Bernadette:)Do you want me to call somebody
at NASA?
(Howard:)No, my mom already tried that.
It only made things worse.
(Leonard:)Gelatinous Sphere.
(Raj:)Focused Locust.
(Stuart:)Temple of Yip.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry,
Wolowitz would never play that card.
(Stuart:)All right, Lesser Demon Turtle.
(Sheldon:)Fairy God Monster, I win.
(Sheldon:)Your desperate need for friendship
makes you weak.
(Raj:)So, what are you guys doing later?
(Raj:)Stuart and I were thinking
of going out for a drink.
(Stuart:)- Try to meet some girls.
- Because that's what we do, heh.
So watch out, ladies, a little coffee
and cream coming your way.